A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, General Administration, Series 5 FA818
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Administration, 1958-1979; 5; 55 Cubic Feet 125 boxes.
  - Wage - Price Freeze, 1971-1973 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Welfare Island Reports, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Welfare Island - Working File, 1972-1974 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Island Project, 1969-1973 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Welfare Island Reports, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Westblock Study, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Woerner, Leah, 1970-1977 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Wolfe, Lester, 1964-1972 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A., 1969 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A., 1970 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A., 1971; 1 of 2 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A., 1971; 2 of 2 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A., 1972-1974 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A., 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S.A.I., 1976-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A. III, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Woodd Cahusac, S. A. II, 1977-1978 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Woods Hole Massachusetts, 1956-1972 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Working Papers, 1972-1976 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Yorkville Youth Work Program, 1971-1974 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Zoning Regulations, 1973-1974 (Box 125, Folder 7)